Hafiz Elfia Wedo Putra

Serang, ID | hafizelfiawedoputra@outlook.com | linkedin.com/in/hafizewp | github.com/hafizewp22

SUMMARY

I have experience in website development at my internship company for one year and I am interested in technology. I am also a hard worker, have integrity, responsibility and work in a team. Really like working in the field of software engineering on coding such as websites and programs to create attractive applications.

EDUCATION

BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY

Jakarta, Indonesia 2019 - Present

Bachelor of Computing in Computer Science

Streaming: Database Technology GPA: 3.33 / 4.0

- Thesis: Design Of Web-Based Learning Media To Improve Learning Systems In Poris Indah Tangerang High School.
- Participated in INC 2020 in a team named GoGainer, and placed 70th ranking of 700 teams National level.
- Winner of Designing UI/UX with Figma Competition (3rd place on campus level).
- Conducting research on Augmented Reality for Human Digestive Anatomy Biology Learning (June 2021) [View]
- The project makes a website-based application about an online store using Laravel 8.0. [View]

EXPERIENCE

PT. TELKOM INDONESIA Web Developer – Internship

Jakarta, Indonesia

March 2022 – February 2023

- Successfully updated the SIIS, MySIISTA and IBAM websites using the ReactJs programming language to add new pages and features to the map, namely GIS (Geographic Information System) and React Leaflet.
- Update API data input from Arcgis on the SIIS 4.0 website and API data input on the IBAM website page.
- I was able to front end create a new website CMS Survey Microdemand to add new page features to the website.

BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY

Tangerang, Indonesia

Student Mentor

October 2021 – February 2022

• The Community Care for Friends at BINUS University which provides the task of helping friends who have special attention and high concern for disability issues and special needs on campus.

ACTIVITIES

BINA NUSANTARA COMPUTER CLUB

Tangerang, Indonesia

Organization - Learning and Training Staff

August 2020 – February 2022

- Establish curriculum and class materials and schedules for classes and teaching.
- Become an event committee in organizations related to Information Technology.
- Create and do attendance for each LnT class.

ADDITIONAL

Hard Skill:

HTML5, CSS, PHP, Javascript, Java, Laravel, ReactJS, Figma (Software), MySQL/SQL, Database Design, Data Analysis, Git, Postman API

Soft Skill:

Teamwork, Time Management, Leadership

Language:

Fluent in Indonesia, Elementary Proficiency in English

Certifications & Training:

CSS (HackerRank, 2023), React Basic (HackerRank, 2022), React - The Complete Guide (Udemy, 2022), HTML Course (Sololearn, 2022), Introduction to HTML5 (University of Michigan, 2022), Database Design and Programming with SQL (Oracle, 2021), Introduction to Back-End Development (Meta, 2022), SQL Basic (HackerRank, 2021), Web Development Path - Node.js (Progate, 2021), Frontend Weekly Workshop (DSC Binus, 2021)

Project:

E-Learning: Poris Indah Smart School (2023) [View], Website Based Online Store "JH Furniture" (2022) [View], Website for Indonesian Covid-19 Data (2021) [View], Clothing Store Cashier Application in Web (2018) [View]